dailyhodl.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy | The Daily Hodl

#### **Your Privacy**

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this privacy policy.

##### **Information Collection and Use**

If you choose to use any services on The Daily Hodl, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, your phone number, your email address and your physical address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.

##### **Log Data**

As a visitor at The Daily Hodl, your browser sends log data. We collect this information which may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address and browser version. It may also include statistical data such as the web pages that you visit at The Daily Hodl, the time and date of your visit, and the duration of your visit.

##### **Consent to the Use of Cookies**

The Daily Hodl uses “cookies” to ensure the functionality of certain website features. Cookies are files that are sent to your browser from a website you visit. They contain small amounts of data used as an anonymous unique identifier and are stored on your computer’s hard drive. The data is not shared or used for any commercial purpose. It is used to give you a seamless experience at The Daily Hodl as cookies are designed to remember preceding events or user interactions, and other user browsing information. You are free to delete these cookies from within your web browser.

By visiting The Daily Hodl, you agree to the use of cookies.

##### **Security of Your Personal Information**

The Daily Hodl and our website hosting platform strive to secure the personal information you provide to us including your name and your email address, but we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Use of the internet exposes all users to a certain degree of risk. Please take measures to secure access to your computer and to your internet access.

##### **Service Providers and Plug-Ins**

We may employ third-party companies and individuals and implement third-party plug-ins. We use the services of these companies, individuals and plug-ins to provide web functionality and to perform services for The Daily Hodl. We also use these services to assist us in analyzing our analytics and data. These third parties have access to your personal information in order to perform the tasks assigned to them on behalf of The Daily Hodl. Our service providers are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any purpose other than to provide web functionality and to perform services for The Daily Hodl as stated.

##### **Links to External Websites**

As a news outlet, The Daily Hodl provides links to third parties that allow visitors to explore topics and investigate companies. These links may be informational or commercial, or they may contain solicitations. By clicking on a third-party link, you will be directed to a site that you are visiting at your own risk. The Daily Hodl does not own or operate any of the sites linking externally, and we assume no responsibility for third-party business practices, content or any measures to maintain your privacy. Please review the privacy policy of these websites, including ad networks, to determine how they will use your information.

##### **Ad Networks**

We use the following ad networks that link to external websites. We strongly advise that you do your own due diligence regarding any investments you may choose to make at your own discretion. We do not endorse, represent, own or are a party to any of the companies in these ad networks. Please review the privacy policies for these ad networks to determine how they are using your personal information: [Google Adsense](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites), [Coinzilla](https://coinzilla.io/privacy-policy/), [Cointraffic](https://cointraffic.io/privacypolicy).

##### **Children’s Privacy**

The Daily Hodl focuses on cryptocurrencies and blockchain technologies, and includes information related to trading and investments. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If you discover that anyone under the age of 13, including your child, has provided us with personal information, we will delete it. If you have any concerns about any information that was unintentionally provided to us, please email us at feedback@dailyhodl.com.

##### **Changes to Privacy Policy**

Please check our privacy policy periodically as we may update it at any time. Any changes to the policy are effective immediately.

##### **Contact Us**

Please email us at feedback@dailyhodl.com if you have any questions, suggestions or comments.
